大家好,我是今天的主播Niko Hello everyone, I am today's host, Niko.
Today, we are going to talk about the production of Hanfu Qixiongshanchen.
Now, let's get started with today's live broadcast.
First of all, we are going to talk about a model, Kelly Jinlan.
Then, here we need to change her posture from A pose to T pose.
This is mainly to make it easier for us to make a Hanfu arrangement.
So here, you can use the X-Ren combination point to make a change in the posture.
Then we are going to make a Hanfu board.
Because
we don't have a direct board for Hanfu, so we are going to use the drawing method here to make a Miao board.
So here is a straight board and then we are going to pour the Hanfu board into it.
What you need to pay attention to here is to enlarge it by 1 to 1.
How do you look at 1 to 1?
You can use the 2D measurement tool to look at it.
And the numbers on it.
Is it the same?
If it's the same, then now it's a ratio of 1 to 1.
Then you can use one of our internal lifting tools and the internal multidirectional tool.
To draw our Hanfu board.
Now, what do we do with its collar?
The inner part is already drawn to make the character.
Now draw a part of its front part.
What about here?
We can use the internal multidirectional tool.
We can use the control button to draw a drawing at the curve.
If you draw a wrong line or a wrong line,
you can delete it in the Delete section.
What about here?
You can delete it.
In this case, you can use the delete button.
Because here we can draw it well
After drawing it well
Let's draw other panels
The methods here are the same
Let's draw its collar
Embroidery and its embroidery
After drawing, you can use the Edit Curve tool
To change the shape of the curve
After drawing, we need to engrave these panels as panels
Here you can choose its internal shape
Then engrave it
Why don't you engrave it here? Because I have a breakpoint
If there is a breakpoint, you need to merge this part with the breakpoint
If there is a breakpoint
You can also convert it to a free-range point
Here I will convert it to a panel
After drawing the collar, you can remove its previous curved panel
And copy the other half of it
After copying, you need to arrange these panels on the virtual model
Here, because its Hanfu panel is more special, we can use the positioning ball tool to arrange it directly
You need to rotate its angle and
Adjust its direction
When arranging here, what you need to pay attention to is that you need to
If you are using a screen coordinate positioning ball, you need to turn it from time to time
Change the direction and then look at the location it is arranged
After arranging, a seam is made below
The seam here is very simple
And the unnecessary panel can be re-enacted
Let's adjust the position
After adjustment, simulate
Now we have this
The straight collar is done
Then sew other places that are not sewed
Next, we will start to sew its collar part
The same
We use positioning ball
Arrange it in the corresponding position
Then adjust its position
Then, because my collar may be slightly longer
Here you need to add its internal line
Fold it
Let it adjust
After adjustment, there is a part of the fold
So you can
Make it hard
Then we will do another simulation
In this way
The top is roughly completed
Our command point
Showing the mountain
There is still a part of the front
The butterfly knot of the rope
And we
Take a look
Adjust its shape
Now we will make a part of the butterfly knot of the collar
In front of it
Here we can draw two small panels directly
Then sew it on top
The fold angle is the fold angle of the collar
The fold angle of the collar is a angles of the collar
That is
The part of the front protruding
Set up the angles
Then. After it has its other half. Copy it out
Move its position
Here it is
We
The butterfly knot can be used directly in the library
And then you can see it here
There are two models of vpac and trim
That trim is a secondary key
So if we can
I want to make the butterfly knot a real simulation
You can add it as a clothing document
Just add it to it
And then we're going to sew it together
Here, let's adjust it a little bit
Its length may be a little long
After adjustment
We're going to sew it up
Here you can add two internal threads directly
Sew it up
Front and back
Then you can close it
After the seam is finished
Take a look at the simulation now
My butterfly knot can be simulated in the same way
Then in order to make it easier for us to do the back
We're going to put it first
Threads are the following
Coat it with his particles
A little less
And then the winding line on the collar
We made him add two
Internal threads
It looks a little more round
And now let's do it again
Its one
Embroidery part
There is a fold here
Put it in the corresponding position of the hand
Then adjust its angle
After adjustment
Here you have to use the fold tool to fold
Then sew
In this way, our whole top one is done
Then we are going to make its KUN
Which is its square
Draw a rectangle in the same way
Then set a 1 to 1
Draw its board for it
Here you can use the internal multi-sided tool
If you encounter a curve
Then you can press the Ctrl key
Now it is a curve
Then we will change its position as a cloth
After that
All of them are classified as boards
Then the board is there
And it's still 1 to 1
Here now I can put it here
Now I can put its top one in this way
Then do its KUN part
This is its box
Because look at this box
It's also a bit
So you have to use it
Adjust it with the positioning ball tool
Here it is not suitable to use
Arrange some tools to arrange
We just use the positioning ball tool to arrange
Arrange
Just arrange it around the model
Then make a seam
This seam is very simple
Then the same part of its waist
There is also a fold part here
Then we can add an internal line
Fold it over
And here
I set the level for it
Because mine
It's in my top
One inside
So I set it up for him
One layer
When you wear it
It will go in directly
The pants are a bit off
So I added a elastic
So the pants are done
What's next
Do this
This whole
The most complicated part of the chest
Is its waist
That is, the broken skirt
That's what you're talking about now
When doing the broken skirt
We need to measure it first
A amount of the chest
The size of the chest
What about here
Its chest is 80.6
Then
And measure the distance from the bottom of the chest to the foot
To determine
Our one
The waist length of the broken skirt and the length of the skirt
Here
Our waist length is set to 116 centimeters
The length of the skirt is 125 centimeters
The skirt is 6 meters
The broken skirt is a T-shape
So let's draw one for him first
Rectangular
What is the size of the rectangle?
Because I did a 12-point circle
So
The length and width of my rectangle
That is, the waist length divided by 12
And the size of the skirt divided by 12
So
The length and width of my rectangle is
596.7
And 125 centimeters
Let's draw our rectangle
After that
Our broken skirt is a T-shape
So you need to divide it up
Then
It will be divided into two T-shape
One is 96.7
One is 500
Then
Let's divide it up
After dividing
Let's connect these two points
Then
Cut it
After cutting
Now
These two
The T-shape is done
That is, our broken skirt
A skirt
Because it's a 12-point skirt
So
It has 12 such skirts
Let's adjust its position
Adjust it
You can rotate it
Ok
You lose it
You need to make it the same
Put the T-shape to the right
And put the T-shape to the left
Then we can adjust the order
The new T-shape
This is a very small T-shape
But the morning
At the beginning we put the T-shape
We will put it in the model
Same place
There is a 2D arrangement
Here
Then
This will be the same as the chops of our windows
The way it is placed is the same
So
Use theabilities ball
Arrange it around the virtual model
around it
and then sew it together.
When sewing, you will see that
it is a little more
and a little more,
so you need to cut it here.
And you can see that
there is no dot on its sewing line,
so you can use a function of the sewing line
, that is, at the beginning and end points of the sewing line,
you can add a short point.
Then we will repeat these two lines in front of us
and copy the remaining ten pieces of it.
Here, I also copy it out
and then arrange it on our model.
Here,
the 2D window is actually here.
The place is not exactly the same.
So sew it together.
I want to add a point to it,
because it is a T-shaped T-shaped,
so it has one side,
it will be a little longer,
so I want to cut it off.
After that,
let's cut these two panels.
Here, I adjusted the position at the 2D window,
and then at the 3D window,
arrange it on a model.
Here, it is also done with the positioning ball.
This is an arrangement done with the positioning ball.
Because you take a look at this broken group of panels,
it is particularly large,
so it is not very good to use the arrangement tool,
so you can directly use the positioning ball to adjust its position.
So let's copy the other few panels to it.
Because when adjusting here,
it may need a little patience,
because it is very easy to penetrate the clothing if it is not done.
So let's copy the other few panels to it.
Do the same for it.
Let's make a seam for it.
Now there are 8 pieces,
and 4 pieces are left.
Then we also copy it out.
When arranging here,
be sure not to mix it up.
Because if it is mixed up,
it is very easy to penetrate when you model.
Now there is only one piece left.
Let's copy it out.
For the last piece,
we also need to delete the excess part.
Now let's go to our 3D window
and make a position adjustment.
Now there are 12 pieces,
all of them are done.
Now we are going to start the simulation.
When we are doing the simulation,
in order to prevent it from falling down,
we add a fixed pin on it.
Just simulate it like this,
and it's done.
Here we can harden it.
Next,
we are going to start adjusting the position of our skirt.
And we are going to make a skirt head.
Then we sew it up.
After sewing it up,
we also add an inner line to it.
Then we use a folding tool to fold it.
Then here,
we use a physical element for the skirt head.
It is toFiscalRegion.
You can make it a little harder.
Then,
and set it up.
In this way,
you can make sure it is in the outer layer.
Here,
you need to adjust the shape of the skirt with a fixed pin little by little.
We can adjust it.
In the simulation state,
as long as you hold the fixed pin,
you can adjust its position and its shape.
Here,
if we say,
you can use our pin pin tool
and the pin pin
fixed on the virtual model,
such a tool,
to fix its position.
Here,
you can keep adjusting it
and you can set the length of the pin pin.
To set, adjust,
and control its distance.
The front is almost adjusted.
Now,
let's adjust the back.
Adjusted.
After that,
let's adjust the shape of the back.
Now,
it's almost adjusted.
Then,
here,
we,
can use the pin pin
to fix the back of it.
Because it's easy to fall off if you don't pull it.
So here,
you need to keep using your pin pin tool
and the pin pin tool
to adjust its position
and its appropriate angle.
Here,
let's sew it a little bit.
If you want to see the effect of sewing after sewing,
you can turn it off.
You can see the effect of sewing.
On the side,
let's fix it a little bit.
Adjust the shape of the skirt a little bit.
Like this.
The skirt and the skirt are almost done.
In order to prevent my skirt from falling off,
here,
I increased its friction rate.
Then,
we're going to start doing the belt part of the skirt.
Draw the same
with the pin tool.
With the pin tool,
you can draw these two small curved plates.
Now,
we're going to do the belt part.
So,
when we're drawing,
we drew a long plate
and a short plate.
Then,
add a pin to its four sides.
adjust its position with a pin.
Then on the short piece,
we adjust the Golden Curvesstäkulostrate,
and let it confess.
To make it easier for us,
a better one and a twist.
You can see the effect.
Here,
we just use this long piece
for the short piece,
and the effect of a curve.
You need to pay attention when drawing a curve.
You need to pay attention
when drawing a curve.
It needs to be paused from time to time, so that once the wave is penetrated, it will have the opportunity to perform a counterattack.
And you need to look at the direction of other angles from time to time.
Here you need to keep rotating its angle.
Here I use the positioning tool to make a wave.
When adjusting the position of the wave, it needs to be slightly lighter here, otherwise it will penetrate immediately.
And when doing it, you need to reduce the strength of these two plates first.
Now we are reducing the thickness of the collision, so that the rope is a little tighter.
There is enough space.
Your knot is always scattered, will it have anything to do with your particle diameter and the thickness of the collision?
If your particle diameter is too large, some of its details will not be shown.
And the thickness of the collision should be slightly larger at the beginning, so that there is enough space between them.
In the process of doing it, you need to reduce the thickness of the collision little by little, so that it will not be scattered.
Now let's reduce it a little bit more.
Here I also slightly adjust its direction.
To make it look more realistic.
Here I mainly use the positioning tool and the fixed needle tool to adjust it.
This is almost done.
Here I applied a default fabric to it.
In the same way, we will adjust its friction coefficient a little bit.
Let it reduce a slide.
Next, we are going to start doing another part of the belt.
We need to draw out the other plates of the belt as well.
I want to draw out the plates here.
It's all done with the lifting tool and the folding tool.
After the position is done, we will also make it a seam.
Seam to the corresponding position.
When sewing here, it may be a little bit more careful.
Otherwise, it is easy for the front loop to conflict.
So here we can fix the loop of the loop.
Or you can add a fixing needle.
Because I added a friction coefficient, I didn't soften it here.
The other side of it is not pointed out.
Because this belt is from one side of the loop.
One side of the loop.
Let it go to the other side.
So let's talk about the other side of it.
Also made it.
It needs to go to the back.
When you sew here, you can use the fixing needle.
So when you do Hanfu, the common tools are the fixing needle.
And our sewing needle tool.
Here, a lot of it is to adjust its shape.
You can adjust the shape of the sewing needle.
Here, in the simulation state.
You can press the W key and add a fixing needle.
If you don't want to use the fixing needle.
You can press the W key to delete the fixing needle.
Because the panel is not long enough now.
So I made it a little bit longer.
After adding the fixing needle.
Just sew it directly.
Here, there may be a little bit of a wrong direction.
Adjust it a little bit.
Then when you do some of these small details.
You can freeze other panels for it.
For example, like clothes, skirts, pants.
Here, you can freeze it.
So your simulation speed will be a little bit faster.
So this side is done.
The other side.
We did it in the same way.
What's next?
I'm going to do the knee.
A double eye knot.
One effect.
Here, the double eye knot.
You can make a real knot.
You can also make a sewing box.
Here, what I'm doing is a sewing box effect.
This method is a little bit easier.
Just make a sewing box.
Just adjust its shape a little bit.
Then we'll put the next belt on top of it.
So this side is done.
But the rope on top is a little.
When I simulated it, it fell down a little.
You can add a fixing needle.
You can add a fixer to fix it first
Then use the axis of the positioning ball to move it to the front
Just copy it out the other time
With this, the whole Hanfu
The guide line, the embroidered mountain, and its river tank and the broken skirt are done
We need to apply its fabric to it next
Here I'm wearing a kind of fabric
on this side
Look here
I'm doing the embroidery
resign
Again, the same fabric in the system
and I also feel and tell things as soon as the fabric is up top
I changed its friction coefficient
After the material and its color are adjusted
We need to add a pattern to it
What about the pattern here
I used a group flower
Then here
You can find a pattern of a group flower
Then make such a square sequence
Then my group flower is
It has the function of a cherry blossom cloth inside the mouth
Then you can design its material
Here I use the material is
The material of silk color
And adjust the transparency of the whole fabric
Then on the skirt
We also use a pattern for it
Here is also the effect of a flower
Then
Give it a color change
Here you can use
The function of the flower cloth
You can also use
The text inside
You can also use the editing function to adjust it
Here my thinking direction is not the same as other
So I adjusted it
Then use the editing tool inside
To adjust its size
To adjust its direction
Then rotate to adjust its direction
Then adjust the position and angle of the other one
Here you can use the texture editing tool
To adjust the size and angle of this texture
Then I will adjust the other ones
Because what I'm doing here is a
The gap between the broken skirt and the skirt is the same
Then adjust its transparency in the same way
Then I will adjust its size and angle of the other one
After adjustment
We need to lock it in
Come in a posture
What about the posture
You can use the excellent combination before
Give it a posture
Then when adjusting the posture
Before
The quality of these assemblies should be slightly lower
Here you can determine its transparency according to the effect
So here I adjusted its transparency
And the same thing
When adjusting the position
Adjust the position
Then adjust the position
When adjusting the position
Adjust the position
After you touch the left button
Select the left button
So it shows the progress
And adjust the position
You can see that the answer is
Here I adjust
The position
Now if I let the machine
To adjust the position
It can adjust the position
Let's find out
OK
It's just like that
I can see that
I can see the camera
It's just like this
Then adjust the color of the top coat
The color of the top coat here may be a little dark
So I adjusted it a little bit
Make it a little brighter
After adjustment, you can adjust the details of the clothes
And you can improve its quality
Now it's still a low quality state
So you need to adjust the details here little by little
Maybe when I changed the posture just now
The shape of the belt here is a little bit deformed
So adjust its shape
Then adjust its position
When the quality is improved here
We don't want to improve its quality at a glance
You need to change its quality little by little
Otherwise, your clothes will conflict easily
And it's easy to get dirty
Here we first improve the quality of the top coat
After adjustment
After improving the particle strength and its conflict thickness
It's very convenient to adjust to make it straight
What are the options?
You can test the structure that exists here
side by side
The structure fin improves weddings
The structure that is used to adjust it
You're going to go through it
Because of its more structure
So you need to improve its particles layer by layer
Pillar stiffness and its vive alcantar
Then we will adjust the other parts of it
The back of the seam is a little bit off
So let's re-shape it
Adjust its position
This is roughly adjusted
Let's add its particle diameter
The particle diameter can be adjusted from 20 to 15
Adjust to 10
Adjust it little by little
Don't adjust it from 20 to 5 at once
Because if you adjust it like this, your complex clothing will break down easily
In this way, the quality of the whole clothing has been improved
Here, maybe because
Next, let's do a thinning part
Set its length and width
1.5mm
And apply a fabric to it
Because the fabric is boat-shaped
So here I set it up like this
Then arrange it on the suit
On the model
Then here is
It's all inside
Inside
Line
Give it a fold
Then arrange it on the model
Because our
The sewing fabric is a little bit light
So I added a little bit of
Thread
Make it a little bit heavier
Float it down
Then the dress here
This dress
You can use our
A wind control machine to adjust it
Let it do a floating effect
Then here
We also gave it a makeup
This makeup is in the PS
Draw
Then
The skin color of its first part
It can also be adjusted to it
So I can just pour it in
And the skin color of the skin
And the material type of the skin
We changed it to skin
In this way
The skin that comes out of the show
Will be more real
This is our show
Let's take a look at the effect of the show
What's next
We need to do the hair part
Because of this
Hair
I made it with the Koro software
The same first
A model
Then
His hair
Get rid of it
Then
Use the 3D pen model tool
On his head
Give him a change
One of his hair
A plate
Because I'm doing it here
Hot oil massage
Is directly
There is a reference picture
OK
Then
Here
The same
Press the control key
You can draw a straight line
Then
Press the delete key
You can delete
Step back
Then
You can
Edit the 3D pen tool
To adjust its shape
After
Here
Adjust it
You can adjust it well
You can increase the curve point
To adjust its shape
In this way
Half of it
It's almost drawn out
After drawing
Then
You can cut it flat
As a piece of paper
Here
We also
Directly apply it
A texture of hair
Then
The other half of it
Give it a copy
Out
This is the bottom
A part
Then
Here
We lowered it
Its position
And its thickness
And
Model and
Surface
Thickness
Then
Here
We need to borrow
The fixed needle tool
Because
We need to sew it
On the scalp
So
Here
Add a fixed needle
The fixed needle
Has a function
Can be fixed
On the virtual model
So
Let's take a look
It's very close
To the scalp
Then
Here
It's possible
The shape of the ear
It's a little bit
There are a lot of missing parts
So
Adjust it
You need to adjust its shape
Here
Let's adjust its shape again
You can use
The tool
To adjust its shape
Here
We can
Eliminate
Excessive
A curve point
Ok
Then
Adjust the shape of the curve
Adjust it
But
After adjustment
The same
We add it again
Fixed needle
Because here
There may be a breakpoint
So
Some places
Need a little bit
Lower
Also
It is fixed
On the virtual model
So
The part of the skin
Is done
Here
We give it
Set a
Direct angle
Hook it
It will be
More
Smooth
Then
We have
Just
Wrapped
It
And
We have
Just
Wrapped
The three-dimensional brush we just made
The line of the brush
It
Delete it
Here
We have
A layer
To
Make it
A little bit
The effect
Then
I
When the wind is enough
You add
A little more
aerobics
With its
Def upgrading
It means
A vacuum between the plate and the plate
And
Features it
one
Another cloth
What are the differences between this cloth and the second soul
Mainly
Accepted
It
Stabilization is also a way to reduce its posture.
Then let's adjust its shape.
Here, the second part, you can also put a little pressure on it,
so that it can be thrown a little more.
Then here, I will convert its hole type to Thunder.
This is a flat effect.
Then the bottom is Cast Angle.
Then let it be a little thicker.
You need to keep adjusting its shape.
Then we want to make it a little bit thicker on top of it.
So I can adjust its shape here.
Changed its shape.
Here you can directly use the Edit Curve tool to adjust it.
Like this.
It may be a little too big on top.
So I adjusted its shape again.
In this way, it is roughly adjusted to its shape.
Then we have to make it with 5 degrees of hair.
Here, I also made it with a curved version.
Then arrange it on the model.
Adjust the position.
Then use the inner line to draw it.
Then turn it over with a folding tool.
This way, there will be a very good red hair piece.
What about the other half?
At first, it was very difficult.
I also drew it here.
The direction is reversed.
Then fold it over the same way.
The drawing here may be a little wrong.
Here we can cut off half of it.
Then the other half of it is lined up and copied out.
Here we have the other half of it lined up and copied out.
Now we can see that half of the hair piece is almost done.
Then we can see that half of the hair piece is almost done.
It may be a little long.
A slight adjustment of its length.
Just a small adjustment.
The other half can be directly symmetrical and then the middle one can be merged with it.
It's okay to cancel the linkage before the merger.
If there is a groove in the middle here, you can give it these two internal lines, add additional points, and then groove it into a shape.
The same goes for the bottom, give it a groove in a shape.
In this way, the shape will be good.
In the same way, we need to reduce the particle diameter.
When making hair, you need to reduce the particle diameter a little bit.
Now the hair piece may be a little thin, so we need to increase the thickness of the groove.
Everyone is doing it again.
When there is a groove in the hair piece, you need to look at the groove of the hair piece from different angles.
Here, because I glued two internal lines and set the angle of the joint, it is a little tight.
So you can set the angle of the groove a little bit bigger.
In this way, the groove hair piece is done.
Next, we are going to make an electric hair bag.
Electric hair bag
It's the kind of hair volume bag.
We keeping the size of the pagan bag.
Here I am using a hexagon tool for the chemical.
It looks like a powiedział.
It looks like a matches.
Maybe I responder the något is a little too big.
We can adjust here.
As a result, does not look as good as the large hawk ball routes.
It looks a little too big and slightly tight.
All this one is monotonous.
Then we increase the thickness of the tape to make it an electronic bag.
Now you can see that the edges are very round.
Because the curve setting of the edge is 100.
You can adjust the curve setting of the edge.
If the curve rate is 0, it will be very smooth.
If the curve rate is set to 20, it will be a little bit round.
You can adjust the curve setting to 20, it will be smooth.
Now we adjust the curve setting to 20, it will be a little bit round.
You can adjust the curve setting to 20, it will be a little bit round.
After making the electronic hair bag, we may need a real one.
It may be a hair clip, a hair clip to wrap it up.
Here we wrap the electronic hair directly with the hair clip.
You can see that I am directly moving the bag here.
You will see a magical state.
First, we will sew the bag on the top.
Because I added an internal line, if you hide the internal line,
you can't see it in your 3D window.
So let it show.
Adjust the location.
When drawing the position of its inner line here,
you can use its blue assist face to determine its position.
Here let's draw it here.
Let's seal it up.
It seems that the direction of the last sewing line is a little bit opposite.
Let's change it.
Then you will find that this electric hair bag
It penetrates directly into the electric hair bag we just drew.
This is because it is not a virtual model.
So it will penetrate directly.
Here you need to turn the electric hair bag into an OB key.
That is, turn it into a negative key.
Then put it in directly.
When you put it in, you must add the added type here.
Then choose virtual model.
Then adjust its size.
Because if you add a negative key.
The negative key is in conflict with the version.
So it will be the same result as just now.
It is also the same penetration.
So you have to turn it into a virtual model.
The virtual model is in conflict with the version.
So there will be a very good package.
Now you can wrap it up.
Then the length of this piece may not be enough.
Let's make it bigger again.
Here you can choose one side directly.
Then go to the length of this giant.
Then here you need to sew its four ends together.
So that the shape of the package is done.
Here you may need to adjust its position.
The direction may be a little reversed.
The real one should be like this.
Then we still have two kinds of hair.
Need to go through this rice cooker.
Also drew such a giant plate.
When it is exposed.
We are going to make it into such a round plate.
So I drew a giant.
Make it.
Then make such a round shape.
So I drew it here.
I drew a inner line in the middle.
Make it fold.
Then look at it like this.
Take a look at it.
Now it is such a round shape.
The hair you made.
Turn it over.
If you say that when you simulate it.
It will fly accidentally.
Then here you can add a fixer.
Fix it for him.
Then give him a.
Adjust him.
His shape.
So here.
You need to use the pin.
Because of the Hanfu.
His detail part is more.
So many tools used.
All are fixed needles.
And the stepper pin tool.
Then.
Your version.
Most of them need to be modeled.
So you probably.
The tools of the version.
Basically.
It is the same thing.
That's it.
The tool of the plate is basically you will use
Then it may be a little bit big
Then let's adjust it again
When you sit here
You need to keep adjusting it
Its shape and its size
It may be a little bit round
We can make it a little bit narrower
So let's make it a little bit narrower
If you want both sides to become narrower at the same time
You can activate it at its center point
This is a two-sided adjustment
So we have a hair like this
After that, I will directly define it as our current color
And then I will make it a little bit smaller
Then I will make it a little bit smaller
Here may be a little traditional to adjust it
How to define hair and shoes
We will introduce it to you in the next live broadcast
Then here, I will directly define our hair
And then we just made the clothes
Directly add it in
Then here, delete the hair directly for it
Then give it a designated hair
Plug it in
What about our simple hair just now?
It's done
Next, we need to add some of its settings to it
And then some of the purple umbrella effects
The scene will be built up like this
Then we can show the final high-definition picture
Then you can also do some other color effects
Then the live broadcast of this issue will end here
Do you have any other questions?
If you have any questions, you can ask them in the chat room.
Yes, the next issue is about how to define your own hair and shoes
You can bring a three-dimensional earring to the model
That is, you make the earrings into a shell
Then give it directly to her
Just stick it on the model's ear
This is the raw hair
The hole is because the size is small
Does it mean the hole in the hairband?
The hole is not because the size is small
Is because there is no conflict between them
You can just pack it
And then the conflict thickness
It refers to the gap between the board and the board
Usually it can be used
Conflict thickness is used to make it a cotton suit
Where can you learn this software
There are some teaching videos on B station
And you can also learn on our official website
Are the configuration and umbrella made of board
No, this is a direct copy
You can just type it in
What version can be customized for hair and shoes
Now the version of 6.1 is ready
Is there any more questions
Can you explain the wind control
The wind control is in our 3D window
There is a wind control here
And then here we can open it
And then here you can choose a type of it
And then you can adjust its strength
There are changes and frequencies
Here you can set it to a different parameter
And then there's an effect
Here we can take a look at its effect
Now it's a wind control effect
And then adjust the particle diameter or penetrate
You take a look at your model's surface
Is the skin diameter zero
When you first do it
If it's zero
Your model is easy to penetrate
Do the rain suit
The effect of the wind control is to adjust the pressure
Yes, adjust the pressure
Two layers of clothes
Is it also to take the clothes out?
Why didn't I understand
If you say you are two layers of clothes
You need to be in the 3D window
Just put the two layers of clothes together
And then arrange it on the model
And then we're going to do a seam
Of course, you can also use this tool
It's a layer 4 tool
And then set it to
This will reduce his conflict
How do you wear a pleated dress
How do you wear it on your waist
It's actually the same way as pants
You can use the model's belt tool
Or there's one here
There's one here
Oh, I might be in the English version here
So what you might see is in English
You can change it to Chinese
And then here you can use this
Measurement tool
And then on the model
Add a circle of this measurement
And then use the virtual model belt tool
Stick it on the virtual model
And then you can wear the pleated dress
Is the thickness of the clothes the thickness of the elements?
Your thickness
If it means
The thickness of his fabric
It's measured by our measurement
If it's a double-layer display
What about here?
You can adjust
Here?
You can adjust the thickness of his
Turn the panel into a square
Is there a seam line behind the line?
I don't understand this one
I don't understand this question
Can you show it in motion?
If you want to record an animation
You can record an animation first
And then show it
Show this animation to him
You can show the animation
How to adjust the hardness of the fabric
Some versions can't be soft
This is based on your fabric
A physical attribute model
There is a setting
If you use the right fabric
It's okay
Why can't the日字扣 be in the material list?
Do not display
This may be
We haven't added this yet
The attached part of the日字扣
May be added later
Can you share this version?
Our master live class
It seems that his material can't be shared
I'm sorry
This is actually very simple
It's just that you go from the Internet
Such a version
Then use the same method as me
It's okay to draw it out for him
Is there any problem?
Yes, it seems to be in the material list
And then show here
Because we are master live class
So all the files
You can do it yourself. It's very simple.
The dynamic effect of the p-blur.
Because the dynamic effect of the p-blur needs to record the main effect in advance.
So if I'm on the spot right now, I might not be able to show it at the moment.
You want to record the main effect, and then it takes a little bit longer.
After recording the main effect, you still have to show it.
This way, there will be a dynamic video.
The animation dynamic will show a little bit, and then the model will be removed.
How can this happen?
It doesn't usually happen.
I don't know how you do it.
Then you can take a look at the animation video on our B-Plan.
You can take a look at it.
The umbrella is not made by Crow.
It's a model I found.
How to do the p-blur effect.
Do you have the p-blur effect?
Set it to a type of
You will pull it 4-5 times with a fixed needle.
You have to pull it a little bit.
Because it's also a piece of clothing.
So it's going to be torn.
What's the problem?
I actually didn't understand that question.
Let's do it again.
If you change one of its grid types to a square grid,
Now it's a square
The points of the line and the points are the same
Do you want to transfer this done clothing to other software?
If you don't know how to use it, you can follow the tutorial video on our B-line
Yes
If there is no problem, then we will stop this live broadcast
Bye bye, see you next time